In high school, you're told you can do anything you put your mind to.
Zero Day is a crime, drama film directed by Ben Coccio.
Two troubled adolescents chronicle the events that ultimately
lead up to a terrifying assault on their school.
Cal Gabriel, played by Cal Robertson.
Andre Kreigman, played by Andre Keuck.
Prom Goer, played by Serataren Adragna.
Victim, played by Melissa Banks.
Josh, played by Joshua Bednarsky.
Rachel Lurie, played by Rachel Benichak.
Zero Day is a 2002 American found footage drama film written and directed by Ben Coccio and starring Andre Keuck and Cal
Robertson, revolving around a duo planning a  school shooting through the perspective of a video filming camera.
The film explores themes of high school, suicide, explosive, sadism, gun.
The tone is dark and emotional.